Preliminary Guide to the Carl Purington Rollins Papers
Yale University Arts Library
- 2002 Addition, 1903-1974
  - Materials relating to New Clairvaux, Dyke Mill, and Montague Press
    - "A Doggerel Solace on a Rainy Day" by E.H.V. and M.G.R. [containing photographs of Montague, MA, and Dyke Mill], 1909 (Box 2)
    - "A Few Glimpses of Montague, Massachusetts" by E. H. V. [containing photographs of Montague, MA, and Dyke Mill and a hand-drawn map], 1916 (Box 2)
    - New Clairvaux, Dyke Mill, and Montague Press printed materials (Box 2)
    - Montague Press printed items: letterheads, bill heads, and miscellaneous (Box 2)
    - Reproductions of CPR printing, Montague Press (Box 2)
    - General Theological Seminary Bulletin issues with typed notes by CPR (Box 2)
    - Volume containing examples of Rollins's designs and printed works from New Clairvaux, Dyke Mill, and Montague Press, 1903-1911 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous printed items (Box 2)
  - "A Nonsense Book by and for G.P.D.", 1922 (Box 2)
  - Bound volume of issues of The Montague Calendar with typed note by CPR, 1912-1916 (Box 3)
  - Stencils used at Dyke Mill (Box 4)
  - Stencils used at Dyke Mill (Box 5)